I-I'm in love with you,
Sarah Hatoff.
I said it.
Now, get out of here.
If you think I'm leaving
the biggest story of my life,
you're an even bigger idiot
than the one I'm in love with.
You just said that on live TV.
- Ugh. Fine.
- Fine.
- Fine!
Fine!
And now, my beautiful army,
destroy them.
Gooba gabba.
Gooba gabba. Gooba gabba.
Whoa!
Gooba gabba.
Oh, no.
Whoa!
Grampa, Papa's in trouble.
Oh, I'll get right on that.
80HD, Papa's in trouble.
Cool.
Oopsies.
Yeah! Oh!
Looks bad, Dog Man.
We've only been partners
for like six minutes,
but it's been real.
I've matured and I respect you,
even if I'm only saying that
for dramatic impact
and I'm actually still evil
and rotten inside.
Dog Man?
Dog Man.
Wha...
Not in the mouth.
- Petey, look.
- Hold on, hold on.
I know you need to arrest me
for escaping from Cat Jail...
...but there are buildings
causing mayhem out there.
They're destroying the city.
Things can't possibly
get any worse.
Chief, turns out we actually
are out of toilet paper.
We're trapped.
What?
Good dog.
No, stop. Not now. Not now.
Yes. Finish them.
- Everyone, follow Dog Man.
-Me first.
Whoa!
We got a cave-in back here.
Aah! Run!
Climb up. Come on.
Gooba gabba.
Leave my papa alone.
Huh?
Hi, Papa.
No. Li'l Petey, no!
What the... Who's that?
Robo-Cat?
Flippy-ki-yay, Flippy flipper.
- Huh?
Yeah!
Gooba gabba!
Whoa.
-Gooba gabba.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
No! You can't escape me,
you sniveling little...
Come here!
Oh, do-gooders.
Li'l Petey!
Dog Man?
Papa.
Flippy is coming this way!
Oh, Robo-Cat.
Come out and play.
Everybody, clear out.
You'll never get away,
Robo-Cat.
Come on. Let's go.
I'll hunt you down
to my last breath.
What are you waiting for?
I'll never stop
till you're dead, Robo-Cat!
You better run, Papa.
It's me he wants.
Robo-Cat.
Oh, Robo-Cat.
Take him, Dog Man.
I'll create a distraction
and stall the fish.
Papa, wait.
Li'l Petey,
if something happens to me,
just try to be evil and stuff
and do the wrong thing.
- For me.
-Robo-Cat.
But, Papa,
Flippy's gonna destroy you.
I'll be okay, kid.